

- Tokyo, Japan 1580085
- 09029048749
- modajima@indeed.com

## **SUMMARY**

Trustworthy and reliable employee with a wealth of practical experience in a variety of fields including experience as a project lead of initiatives such as "Help Center Article improvement," and designer of the "Kyujin Shindan" project.

## **SKILLS**

- Technical troubleshooting and problem solving
- High-volume call/email handling under fast paced environment
- Professional communication
- Mentoring experience
- Multitasking and prioritization

### **EDUCATION**

2014 **Diploma of Higher Education** | English Kanda Institute of Foreign Languages, Tokyo

# Momoka Odajima

### **EXPERIENCE**

January 2020 - Current

Client Success Specialist Indeed Japan | Tokyo, Japan

- Provides expert support to S-sized clients, partners and fellow teammates around the globe.
- Handles huge number of inquiries, via emails and phone calls, regarding account navigation, helping clients improve the performance of their job listing, and technical troubleshooting.
- Entrusted mentor for new hires uses accumulated knowledge and experience to coach junior employees through adapting to both their work at Indeed and life outside work as new working adults.

July 2018 - July 2019

Guest Service Representative Mitsukoshi USA Inc. | Orlando, FLORIDA

- Served as a cultural representative to ensure visitors were able to fully enjoy and experience Japanese culture and the Disney park.
- Was entrusted with multiple positions including the Guest Service position. Ensured the influx of customers was organized by carefully managing reservation times and providing efficient guidance

October 2014 - July 2018

VIP lounge staff / Front Desk staff Grand Hyatt Tokyo | Tokyo, Japan

- VIP lounge staff while acting as a coaching staff member for new hires
- Attended to VIP guests by performing front desk tasks, reservations, acting as a concierge, phone calls both in Japanese and English, and anything else required to ensure a pleasant stay.
- Operated efficiently in an extremely fast paced environment by maintaining detailed schedules and organizing upcoming tasks
- Handled guest complaints in a rational, calm and professional manner, providing smart solutions to maintain guest satisfaction.

April 2014 - September 2014

Learning Advisor Kanda Institute of Foreign Languages | Tokyo, Japan

- Assisted students in practicing practical english through conversation and advised students about study routines to improve their fluency
- Acted as an classroom assistant with a focus on mentoring and helping struggling students to ensure they succeeded

### ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- I thrive in environments in which I am constantly learning new skills to make today's version of myself better than yesterday's. Outside of work, I enjoy spending my time studying at cafes, taking Udemy courses on design and foreign languages, and I recently graduated from a business academy where I created a personal branding movie.
- I recently joined the leadership team for Women at Indeed in Tokyo. I
  have a deep interest in IRG activities and I am passionate about
  making the work environment a positive space for everyone including
  marginalized employees. In conjunction, I'm currently enrolled in
  several courses to further understand the principles of inclusive
  leadership and asserting oneself to ensure the respect of gender and
  sexual differences.

